Abs, you ready?
Abby...
Abs.
Come on. I know you're in there.
Let's go.
Abby, come on.
Okay, okay.
You're being a jerk.
You know I have somewhere
I have to be.
Come on, let's go.
Five minutes.
I need you dressed.
"And though
the dreamer remains asleep,
"he walks through memory
as if experiencing it
"for the first time anew,
no longer a passenger
but an active participant."
This stuff for real?
Some people think so.
Guess it depends on what you believe.
Summer of '82,
I traded a mint condition
Cal Ripken Jr. rookie
for a used copy of "Missile Command."
That card's probably worth
800 bucks now.
I wish I could participate
in that memory
and actively kick my own ass.
Can I keep it?
No.
I would like the walnut fudge,
but I want the fudge on the side
because I don't want it
to melt the ice cream.
And can I get some whipped cream on top
and three cherries?
Coming right up.
Hey.
You want your usual, right?
Uh, yeah.
So, when are you gonna bring
your sister by?
We got this new flavor,
Rainbow Explosion.
I bet she'll go crazy for it.
Mike?
Hey!
Number 27?
Follow me.
Mm.
What is your deal, Mike?
What are you, some kind of...
...head case?
You beat up a man in broad daylight.
In front of his child.
Daddy!
That was a mistake. Um...
It was a misunderstanding.
I-I thought...
Just look at your employment record.
Tire Zone, sales associate,
two months, terminated.
Insubordination.
Media World, custodial staff,
one week.
It's like you're not even trying here,
yet you sit before me
asking for help.
I am just trying
to figure out who you are,
Mr. Michael Sh...
Hmm.
Coffee?
Sorry?
Uh, would you, would you
like some...
some coffee? I made some coffee.
No.
I'm-I'm gonna be brutally
honest with you here, Mike.
Given your track record,
your options...
are gonna be extremely limited.
- I'll take anything, okay? Any-any job you got.
- No. No.
Look, I-I-I get that part.
Um, it's just...
You know, it's not that easy.
Yeah. Thank you.
I have a job for you.
Come on, sit down.
Sit, sit, sit, sit, sit.
Okay, uh, well, what is it?
It's a security gig.
Full disclosure. It's not great.
Right? High turnover.
That's what we call it
in the business,
but you get to be
your own boss. Sort of.
And you only have to worry
about one thing.
Keeping people out.
And-and, you know,
and keep the place tidy.
That's two things.
You want the job or not?
- How's the pay?
- Not great.
But the hours are worse.
I can't do nights.
Excuse me?
That's such a shame.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Wait, uh...
In case you have a change of heart.
Hey, Max.
Thanks for babysitting.
There's Stouffer's.
Should still be warm
if you're hungry.
I have to tell
you, there is something magical
about these rings,
and you can have it within...
I wish someone would
buy me a ring.
Did Abby eat?
What do you think?
Same time tomorrow?
Yep.
What do we got?
Okay.
Well, that good-looking guy
I recognize.
Who are all these other punks?
My friends. It's not done yet.
Well, look, you can finish up
after we eat, all right?
Come get some food.
I'm not hungry.
Abby, please, come eat.
- Come on. Here. Please come.
- No!
Come and...
Abs, with the day that I'm having,
can you just eat some food?
You're sitting on my friend.
You know what? I don't care.
Do whatever you want.
But you should know
what happens to little kids
who don't eat their dinners.
Their bodies stay
the same size forever.
And they never get to ride
the adult rides at the amusement park.
My friend says you're an idiot.
Mm.
At least I'm real.
How about some burger
with that ketchup, hon?
Everything's better swimming in ketchup.
Right, Mike? Whoop.
I'm gonna go grab a towel.
- Go watch your brother, okay?
- Okay.
Garrett.
Garrett?
Garrett! Garrett!
Just look at my nephew.
It's not even 10:00
and he-he can barely
keep his eyes open.
And this degenerate
is who they entrust
with the well-being
of a mentally ill child.
Jane, like I've said before,
Abby is not mentally ill.
Oh, right.
Perfectly normal to sit around
drawing pictures all day
and-and talking to magical
creatures who do not exist.
Listen, I think we all just need
- to calm...
- Don't tell me to calm down.
You're the doctor,
and you're making me feel like
I'm the crazy one?
And after... after what he did
to that poor man...
I just...
I have really tried to play nice.
I have.
But I have to think about Abby now.
Enough is enough. Doug?
Doug.
- Oh.
In your heart,
you know that this is
the right thing to do.
I hope that you will sign.
- And if I don't?
- Well, then,
my lawyer and I will
have to take you to court,
where any judge
with an ounce of sanity
will see to it that you never
see your sister again.
That what you want?
She-she doesn't even care
about Abby.
All she wants is the
monthly check from the state.
But, I mean, she-she has
some good points, though.
I'm hardly fit to be raising a kid.
I know a little girl
who would strongly disagree.
Come on.
She talks to air
more than she talks to me.
I could drop dead tomorrow,
and she'd be too busy drawing
to even notice.
You know, pictures hold
tremendous power for children.
Before we learn to speak,
images are the most important
tool we have
for understanding
the world around us.
What's real,
what matters to us most.
These are things
children learn to communicate
almost exclusively through pictures.
Yeah, her pictures mean something.
And who is at the center
of nine out of ten of them?
- Me.
- Mm-hmm.
Like it or not,
you're her world.
But what if it's not up to me?
My aunt, she's an idiot,
but she's right.
No judge in their right mind
is ever gonna side with me.
Did you find a job yet?
Okay.
That would be a good place to start.
Hello.
- Uh, hi.
Mr. Raglan, this is Mike.
- Mr. "I can't work nights."
- Right.
Uh, yeah, I was just calling
to see if that job
that you offered was, uh,
was still available.
Oh, it absolutely is.
Why? Have you had
a change of heart?
How soon could I start?
Let me give you
a little backstory.
This place was huge
in the '80s with the kids.
It's been shut down for years.
The only reason
they haven't given it
the old wrecking ball treatment
is the owner's a bit of a...
Well, he's kind of
a sentimental guy, I guess.
Just can't bring himself
to let it go yet.
Yeah.
Had some trouble with break-ins
over the years.
Drunks and vagrants, mostly.
Not ideal.
Security system's dated
but fully functional.
Floodlights on the outside,
cameras inside and outside.
Fair warning:
the electricity is a bit...
iffy.
Anything happens, there is
a breaker in the main office.
Just flip it.
Uh, I guess that's about it.
You know...
the rest is pretty easy.
Just keep your eyes
on the monitors and...
and keep people out.
Piece of cake.
So, I will catch you
on the flip side.
Hopefully.
The hell?
Welcome to Freddy Fazbear's Pizzeria,
a magical place for kids
and grown-ups alike,
where fantasy and fun
come to life.
If you're watching this video,
it means you've been selected
as Freddy's newest security guard.
Congratulations.
We're going to have
so much fun together.
The genius who created
Fazbear Entertainment
opened Freddy Fazbear's Pizzeria
to indulge in
his two greatest passions...
family-friendly fun
and cutting-edge
animatronic technology.
- State-of-the-art robotic engineering
enables our characters
to interact with guests
in truly lifelike fashion,
while cleverly concealed
rechargeable lithium cells
give them limited range
to roam free.
Let's introduce you
to the stars of the show.
Adorable, aren't they?
Protecting these cuddly critters,
and the proprietary technology
that brings them to life,
is now your sacred duty.
Keep them safe, and help ensure
that Freddy Fazbear's Pizzeria
is here to delight,
dazzle and entertain
for years to...
All right.
Hello?
Everything's better
swimming in ketchup.
Right, Mike?
Go watch your brother, okay?
Garrett?
Garrett!
What is this?
Who are you?
That car.
Did you see that car?
You see what happened?
Did you see who took my brother?
Wait! No.
- Hey.
- Hey, Max.
So? How'd it go?
Uh...
it was interesting.
I should probably
get out of here.
Hey, by the way, I-I do intend
on-on paying you, eventually.
It's okay.
I know where you live.
Hey. Welcome to Sparky's.
Could I set you folks up
with some appetizers?
Yes.
Oh.
We are not eating.
Well, that's no fun.
You do realize that lunch
is the most important meal
of the day?
I thought it was breakfast.
Some people say that,
- but, you know, it's just a theory.
- Are you being paid
by the word,
or could we have a minute?
- All right.
- Thank you.
Ah, where were we?
Oh, you were about to tell me
what a miserable failure you are.
Hey, screw you, lady.
My sister went over every inch
of that dump a thousand times.
If there was something to find,
she would have found it.
Now pay up.
Uh, I'm sorry?
You said 200.
We had a deal.
Yeah, that you were gonna find me
hard proof of criminal endangerment.
Instead, you've told me
what a nice kid my niece is
and that my nephew sleeps a lot.
He really does, though.
Sleeping is not a crime.
Is that guy okay?
I just realized I shouldn't
be hearing any of this.
As a matter of fact,
I shouldn't be here at all.
Sit down, Doug.
So, I guess we're finished here,
unless either one of you
has a brilliant idea,
which I realize is highly unlikely.
Why don't we just kill him?
Tempting. But no.
- What else?
- Mike was saying that...
he really needs this new job
to, like, look good on paper
for the judge or something.
Well, that's all
very fascinating, honey,
but I am not hearing a plan.
We toss the place.
- Go on.
- Well, he's a security guard, right?
His job is to make sure
nobody gets in.
So, we get in,
and we mess up the place good.
We help ourselves to whatever
we find along the way.
Your nephew gets canned.
Judge gives you the kid,
and you give us...
$2,000.
One thousand.
But do it fast,
and don't mess it up.
I mean, you know, mess it up,
but don't...
don't mess this up.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Abby, do you need something?
- No.
- All right, quit playing and take that off.
I have to go to work.
I know. I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
- Give me the vest.
- No.
Give me the vest now.
I'm coming with you.
I want to go with you.
Abby.
- I don't want to stay here with Max.
- Abby, stop.
- Hello?
No! You can't make me.
Yes, I can.
- No, it's mine.
Hello?
Let go!
- Let go. No, no.
Abby, stop. Abby.
- He's taking my vest!
- Abby.
I'm keeping it.
- No.
She's all yours.
Garrett!
Wait, please.
Please don't-don't...
don't run.
Okay? I-I just want to know
what you saw.
Please. I'm begging you.
Help me.
Who took Garrett?!
♪ The secrets that you just can't hide... ♪
♪ You tell me that you want me... ♪
About time.
Starting to think maybe
you fell asleep on the job.
Um...
Can I, uh, help you, Officer?
Please, my name's Vanessa.
And you must be?
Um...
- The new security guard.
- Yeah.
You're bleeding, by the way.
Looks nasty.
Come on. I know where they keep
the first aid kit.
Love what
you've done with the place.
Why Nebraska?
- Oh, you need a hand?
- I'm fine.
You sure?
Here.
I'm a certified EMT.
So if your heart ever goes out,
I'm the one you want to call.
You seem to really know
your way around the place.
Well, Freddy's is on my beat.
I like to stay well informed.
Also, I really loved this place
as a kid.
There.
That should do it.
Vanessa Shelly.
Mike.
Pleasure to meet you, Mike.
You doing all right this evening, Mike?
What?
Are you good? Are you okay?
Is everything copacetic?
Yeah, I know what "all right" means.
Do you also know that your eyes
are bloodshot
and your heart rate's
through the roof?
And aside from that gash
on your arm,
which...
let's be honest,
is pretty frickin' bizarre,
you've been acting suspicious
since the moment you opened the door.
Yeah, look, it's been a weird night.
Sounds like Freddy's.
This place, it gets to people.
It's one of the reasons why
you're gonna quit.
I'm sorry?
Oh, yeah.
You security hires, you never last.
Have you met them yet?
Met who?
So, what are the other reasons?
Huh?
Why you think I'm gonna quit my job?
Well, you tell me.
Is this somewhere you see yourself
10, 20 years from now?
I mean, what do I know?
Maybe the benefits are great.
- I didn't think so.
Add to that the thing
with those kids going missing.
Wh-What did you just say?
Prepare to have your mind blown.
♪ When you close your eyes ♪
♪ And you go to sleep ♪
♪ Sleep, sleep, sleep ♪
♪ And it's down to the sound
of a heartbeat ♪
This... this is...
The best thing you've seen
in your entire life?
♪ I can hear the things
that you're dreaming about ♪
♪ About, about, about ♪
♪ When you open up your... ♪
- Want to dance?
Maybe some other time.
Wait, y-you said
some kids went missing?
Sure. Back in the '80s.
What happened to them?
It was big news.
That's why the place shut down.
Wow.
You really didn't do
your homework, did you?
And you're not even
wearing your badge.
Got it.
There.
Now you're official.
Hey.
Some friendly advice?
Don't let this place get to you.
Just do your job, and you'll be fine.
Yeah, sounds good.
JEFF
It's showtime.
As soon as he gets back,
get the guys and meet me here.
I think I see a way in.
All right.
Now, be quick but thorough.
Maximum damage, minimum time.
You see anything valuable,
grab it,
and we'll, uh, settle up after.
- Good?
- Yeah. Golden.
Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Let's go, boys!
- Come on!
Carl?
Hank?
What the hell are you doing?
- Hank!
- Jeff?
Jeff!
Come on, you stupid...
Hank?
Come on. Come on.
Shit.
No! No! No!
Jeff?
Carl?
Hey.
Follow me.
Hey!
Hey, wait!
Come on.
Hello?
This way.
Warmer.
How in the heck?
It's feeding
time for the giraffe.
Hey, Abs, what you working on?
All right.
I guess you don't want this, then.
It's cool, huh?
Okay.
I'm trying my best, Abby, okay?
Can't you read?
You okay?
I made a mess.
I'm sorry.
They're just...
they're just papers, all right?
They don't...
they don't mean anything.
Then why do you have them?
Well, that's complicated.
Aunt Jane...
I hate her.
She's mean and she smells
like cigarettes.
It's not funny.
You're right, it's not.
It's just, uh...
I don't know, it's nice that
we can finally agree
about something.
Are you gonna
give me away?
Abs, no, I...
Hey. Vanessa.
Hey, Mike.
And hello.
Vanessa, this is Abby.
Abby, Vanessa.
Hi, Abby.
Mike didn't tell me
he had a daughter.
- Gross.
- No, uh, Abby's my sister.
Ah. Well, he didn't tell me
he had a sister either.
Are you here to arrest Mike?
Okay, uh, can you
go play in your room
so me and Vanessa can talk?
It's nice to meet you.
What, um...
what are you doing here?
- Somebody broke into Freddy's.
- What?
Wh-What-what happened?
Recognize these?
Look, it's not
what you think, okay?
Th-Those are--
They're sleeping pills.
- They help me sleep.
- I know what they are, Mike.
It's written on the bottle.
News flash...
If you're too whacked out
to remember to lock
a friggin' door,
accident or not, you're liable.
It's called criminal negligence.
You wouldn't understand.
Well, then help me.
'Cause the moment I file that report,
it's out of my hands.
You want to take a walk?
So I used to have a brother.
His name was Garrett.
And when I was...
about 12,
he was, uh, he was taken.
And I was there when it happened.
They never found the guy who did it,
and they never found my brother.
So there's this theory that,
uh, we can't forget things.
Basically, it says that
every single thing that you see
in your entire life,
down to the tiniest of details,
gets stored inside of you.
You just have to know how to look.
Your brother--
you think you saw who took him?
I know I did.
And I know that he's in here,
but he's just-- he's--
It's buried.
So every night, I dream,
and I go back to that same memory,
and I-I search for details.
For any little thing
that got overlooked.
Yeah.
And that's usually the part
where people tell me I'm crazy.
I know what crazy looks like, Mike.
This isn't it.
Not even close.
And these?
I mean, going back to the same dream,
the same place night after night,
it's not easy,
so the-the pills help.
Some other things,
like familiar sights,
familiar sounds.
"Pining for fun?"
"Visit Nebraska."
Your sister seems cool.
So it's just the two of you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just us.
Our mom died a little while back.
And Dad, he couldn't handle it,
so...
You know what's crazy is, uh,
when... when Garrett and I
were kids,
they were like
those perfect parents
you'd see on old TV shows.
Yeah, ev-every night,
we would sit down together,
we'd have family dinner,
and we'd hold hands
and say grace, and...
That actually sounds really nice.
Yeah, at the time,
I thought it was really cheesy.
But then it's gone.
You and Abby,
you still have each other.
From where I sit,
I'd say you're lucky.
I should go.
No more sleeping on the job.
When you're at Freddy's,
you stay alert.
Hey, it's Max.
Leave a message. Or don't.
Come on, Max. Come on.
Hey, it's Max. Leave a mes...
I will work,
and you will sleep,
and under no circumstances
are you gonna come out
of my office.
- Do you understand?
- I understand.
This is not a vacation, okay?
You're not here to have fun.
Okay.
- Whoa, slow down, slow down, slow down.
- No, no, no.
Abby?
Whoa.
What happened?
Give me your hand.
Watch out.
Do you want me
to turn the light off?
Okay.
Good night.
It's like camping.
Abby?
I'll be right back.
Hello?
I know you're back there.
Might as well come out.
You're those kids, right?
The ones who disappeared?
Look.
I don't know how it's possible
that you're here
like this in my dream, but...
...I need your help.
Please.
Help me remember
the man who took my brother.
If we show you,
what will you give us?
Anything.
I'll give you anything you want.
Abby?
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Mike.
They wouldn't stop tickling me.
I thought I was gonna die.
Freddy, this is my brother, Mike.
- Abby, what is this?
Come on.
I want you to meet the others.
Mike, this is Bonnie,
Foxy and Chica.
Everyone,
this is Mike.
This-this is a joke, right?
I mean, th-there's someone here.
There's probably somebody
controlling them, right?
I mean...
Okay, good joke!
Congratulations! You got me!
You can come out now!
Hello?
It's okay, Mike.
They just want to play.
- We have to go home now. Come on.
- Hold on.
They really like pictures.
I had a lot of fun tonight.
Thank you for playing with me.
Okay, okay, Abby, come on.
Okay.
Bye!
There you go.
It's them.
Hey, Abby, um,
we need to talk about
last night, okay?
Um...
So those, uh, those...
machines...
My friends?
Your friends?
Um...
are they...?
Ghosts?
- Yeah.
- Of course.
How else could they make
the robots move?
Right.
Can I have some more soup?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, Abs.
You know we used to have
a brother, right?
Garrett.
I don't... I don't really
talk about him very much.
Neither did Mom or Dad.
Yeah, it was hard for them.
It's hard for me, too.
C-Can you explain this to me?
You-you drew that, right?
Okay, and... and-and
you know what that is?
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Okay, I'm not, I'm not mad.
I won't get angry at you.
But I really need you
to help me understand, please.
That's when Garrett got taken.
Abby, who told you about that?
W-Was it a-a boy
with blonde hair?
Did that boy
ever tell you anything
about the man driving that car?
Anything at all?
Okay, just think,
think really hard, okay?
No.
All they talk about
is a yellow rabbit.
Okay.
But...
I can ask.
I would really appreciate that.
♪ We love the yellow rabbit ♪
Vanessa's here.
Yeah.
My friends talk about her sometimes.
- What do they say?
- That she's nice.
Abby, if I asked you
to wait in the car, would you?
No.
Abby, wait.
Guys, I'm back.
- Abby.
- Hey, Vanessa.
Abby.
- Mike.
- Vanessa.
I missed you guys.
You knew about this.
Guess you figured it out.
Ghost children possessing giant robots?
Thanks for the heads-up.
Guys, we need help.
It needs to be big
so we can all fit inside.
Abby, look.
Now, this is all really fun
and exciting,
but these things are big,
and they could be dangerous,
so I think we need to lay
some ground rules, all right?
Vanessa, what do you think?
I think we could use the tables
for the fort.
Everyone, follow me.
Come on.
♪ Riding on any wave ♪
♪ That is the luck you crave ♪
♪ They don't believe it now ♪
♪ They just think it's stupid ♪
♪ So got anything? ♪
♪ Anyone could have done ♪
♪ Who would've cared at all... ♪
It needs to be higher.
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ How a heart is a spade ♪
♪ But somehow the vital ♪
You did it!
♪ Connection is made... ♪
Are you okay?
I like it in here.
Me, too.
But I think it's gonna rain soon.
Sounds like we need a roof.
I'll go see what I can find.
I'll, uh...
I'll-I'll come with you.
Abby, don't forget to ask.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
What are you looking for, exactly?
Tablecloths.
They used to keep 'em back here
for big events.
Right. And remind me how
you know that.
Found 'em.
Don't.
I wouldn't do that.
They're spring locks.
They're on all the older models.
They were designed
to keep the animatronic parts
in place so that, uh, a person
could safely wear the suit.
They tend to be pretty unstable.
Let's see.
Ooh.
Like I said, unstable.
Is there anything else that you
want to tell me about, Vanessa?
'Cause you seem to know
everything about this place.
And what if Abby'd come in here?
What if she'd found that thing?
You're the one who brought her,
Mike, not me.
What I can't wrap
my head around is why.
All right, look.
I think that they know
who took my little brother.
I can't explain it,
but when I'm here,
I feel closer to Garrett.
My dreams are more vivid,
and it...
it's like I can almost...
Change what happened?
Did you ask them about this?
Yeah, I tried.
I don't think
they like me very much.
But...
...they do like Abby.
Mike, you need to drop this.
I don't really see how
that's any of your business.
I'm telling you,
you need to let it go.
Who the hell are you?
Just someone
who's trying to help.
♪ Well, I'm just out of school ♪
♪ Like I'm real, real cool ♪
♪ Got to dance like a fool ♪
♪ Got the message that
I got to be a wild one ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, I'm a wild one ♪
Vanessa, wait.
♪ Gonna break it loose... ♪
- Talk to me.
- I'm trying.
You're not listening.
Please.
Finding the guy that did this
is the only thing
that matters to me.
Abby?
Wait. Abby, don't!
Abby? Abby!
- What happened?
It's okay, Abby.
You just had an accident.
You're okay.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Just go home, Mike.
Take care of your sister.
What are you so afraid of?
In the storage room...
I saw your eyes.
You were terrified.
You can do whatever you want
with your own life,
but if you ever bring Abby
back here again,
I will shoot you.
She looked so angry.
Why does everyone always
look at you that way?
- Hey, it's Mike.
I need your help.
Abby.
Is that bacon?
Hey, why don't you, uh, get dressed
and then come to the kitchen, okay?
I want to talk to you
about something.
Okay.
Wow, there's my favorite
little girl.
Come have a seat, all right?
What did you do?
Abby, look, I think
if you just sit down,
we can explain it to you, okay?
No.
I promise you, this is not
what you think it is.
I hate you.
I hate you, Mike!
Well, I-I think that went well.
She reminds me of you, you know.
Always with the temper.
Well, look, when she calms down,
can you, um, tell her that I'm sorry
and that I'll-I'll be back soon?
Well, Mike,
there's a larger conversation
that needs to happen here.
So when you do get back,
you and me are gonna have
a little chat.
Okay.
♪ Celebrate good times, come on ♪
♪ Let's celebrate ♪
♪ Celebrate good times... ♪
You know what works for me?
A warm glass of milk
with chamomile and honey.
I tell you...
What an asshole.
Okay, enough games, you two.
Emergency landing.
Coming in.
- Hey, buddy.
Well, don't just stand there.
Dig in.
Sweetheart, what's wrong?
This... this isn't...
this isn't how it happened.
This isn't real.
But it could be.
What is this?
This isn't what I asked for.
But it's what you want.
No. I just, I just want
to find the man that...
You're lying.
You want to save Garrett.
That's why you're really here.
To change what happened.
To go back.
But I can't.
He's gone. They're all gone.
Really?
You can have this dream every night.
You can be together
with him again.
Like before.
How?
You said we could have
anything we wanted.
We want Abby.
Abby?
They love her, Mike,
and she loves them.
You've seen her with them.
You've seen how happy she is.
It's time to let her go, sweetheart.
You were never the right person
to take care of her.
Okay.
Yes.
You're home.
No.
No, this is wrong.
I don't, I don't want this.
Listen...
I made a mistake!
Please, I don't want this!
Do you hear me?!
You leave Abby alone!
Abby.
Stay away from my sister!
- Abby.
Abby.
Abby. Abby.
Abby. Abby. Abby.
Abby.
No!
Abby?
You can't stay in there
forever, you know.
Suit yourself.
The pottery that grows.
It's easy.
Soak your Chia overnight,
spread the seeds...
Oh.
Freddy?
Not Freddy.
They're all waiting for you.
It's time to go play.
Silly Aunt Jane.
She fell asleep.
How do we get there?
♪ I wanna be down ♪
♪ With what you're going through ♪
♪ I wanna be down... ♪
Where to, little lady?
What the...?
Oh, my goodness!
Not cool.
Why do I always get the weirdos?
Careful.
I managed to stop the bleeding,
but you're probably
gonna need stitches.
Where are we?
Police supply outpost.
I found you,
and, uh, you were...
you were badly hurt.
They tried to kill me, Vanessa.
But I'm guessing
you already knew that.
Max.
Her brother.
You knew about them, too, right?
- It's complicated.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
More complicated than
possessed robots
murdering innocent people?
They weren't innocent.
Yeah, Abby is!
- Mike...
- You saw Abby playing with them.
And you knew
what they were capable of,
- and you didn't say anything!
- Mike, please just...
Abby is in danger!
Tell me what happened.
In my dream...
...they asked me for Abby.
And I said yes.
It was a mistake,
and I-I tried to fix it, but...
What do they want
with my sister?
They want to make her like them.
Come on, let's go.
Where'd you go?
In the '80s,
when those kids went missing...
...the police searched Freddy's
from top to bottom.
Every inch was accounted for.
But they never found them.
Hello?
The man who took them,
he was a...
He was a very bad man.
A very cruel man.
Also a very clever man.
He knew that parents would cry,
and the police
would come looking.
And he knew there's one place
they'd never think to check because...
...why would they?
I mean, why would anyone?
It's not just their ghosts that
are inside of those machines.
It's their bodies.
You have to understand, the...
the kids, they don't want
to hurt anyone.
It's-it's him.
He influences them somehow.
He took everything from them,
but they don't remember.
Who, Vanessa?
I tried to warn you.
I really did try in my own way.
But it's too late now.
He knows that
you're looking for him.
He'll be coming.
You need to tell me who he is.
His name is William Afton.
He's my father.
You knew?
Mike...
This whole time.
My brother, you knew.
Not about Garrett, no.
A-At least...
not when we met.
I'm so, so sorry.
Tell me how to stop them.
Tell me how to save my sister!
Electricity.
Electricity is the key.
We use these for animal control.
There's a Taser on your belt.
It won't do permanent damage,
but it'll mess with
the animatronic circuitry.
Hopefully buy you some time.
Come with me.
No.
Vanessa, you owe it to me,
and you owe it to them.
No, I can't.
If he's there, I...
...I won't be any use to you,
believe me.
He really messed you up,
didn't he?
Take these.
You need to avoid
the front entrance.
There's an outlet vent
on the east side of the building.
That's the best way inside.
♪ You tell me that you want me ♪
No.
♪ You tell me that you need me ♪
♪ You tell me that you love me ♪
♪ And I know that I'm right ♪
♪ 'Cause I hear it in the night ♪
♪ I hear the secrets that you keep... ♪
♪ Don't you know you're sleeping... ♪
Abby.
Chica, where are we going?
♪ And I know that I'm right ♪
♪ 'Cause I hear it in the night ♪
♪ I hear the secrets that you keep ♪
♪ When you're talking in your sleep ♪
Chica, I don't like this.
Let go of me!
Abby?!
Chica, let me go.
Hey!
Leave her alone!
Mike.
Hey.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I don't know what's wrong with her.
I don't know why she was
trying to hurt me.
I know. I know.
Hey, Abby, listen to me.
I've been an idiot
about so many things.
I've been stuck
trying to fix the past,
but you are the most important
thing in the world to me,
and I promise you
I'm gonna do better.
I love you, too, Mike.
But we should probably go now.
Right, okay. Come on.
Mike!
Run! Hide! Abby, go!
Abby?
Abby, where are you?
- Vanessa.
- It's okay.
Foxy.
I need to get you somewhere safe
so I can go help
your brother, okay?
You couldn't just
leave it alone, could you?
Lucky me.
This is perfect.
First I killed your brother.
Now I kill you.
Symmetry, my friend.
Go to hell.
Wake up, children.
I have something for you
to play with.
This is gonna be so much fun.
Little ones tell me
you have a sister.
She will love it here.
You, however, are finished.
Farewell, Michael Schmidt.
That's enough!
Drop the knife.
A little old for temper tantrums,
aren't we, Vanessa?
I'm not kidding, Dad.
You may have forgotten your
loyalties, but I assure you,
they have not.
Mike!
Please wake up.
Now, put that thing away
and help me clean up the mess
that you created!
Please.
Please, Mike. Please. No!
Come on.
We both know you're not gonna use a...
Mike. Mike.
Abby. Abby.
The Yellow Rabbit,
he controls them.
The drawings.
The Yellow Rabbit hurt your friends.
Show them what really happened.
You had one job.
One.
Keep him in the dark
and kill him
if he got too close.
That's two jobs.
- No!
- Let go!
I won't let you hurt her, too.
Dad.
Hey.
What have you done?
They can see you now.
They know what you did.
Move.
Move!
Mike!
Look at you.
Look at the nasty things
that you have become.
Look how small you are,
how worthless you are.
You are wretched,
rotten little beasts.
I made you!
I always come back.
What is happening?
The spring locks.
Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
- Okay, one more.
- Oh, wait, one more?
- Put one more? One more block?
- Yeah.
- One more block?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's do one more.
It's really extraordinary,
the turn she's taken
these past few weeks.
Whatever you're doing,
keep doing it.
Yeah, I will.
It's not that hard.
What do you want for dinner?
Pizza or spaghetti?
Both.
You got to choose. Which is it?
But I want both.
You can't have both.
Spaghetti with meatballs.
All right, with meatballs.
Um, we're gonna make
a quick stop, okay?
Vanessa, I don't know if...
you can hear any of this,
but, um...
...I'm having a hard time just
processing everything that happened.
But you were there for me and Abby
when it mattered the most.
And I don't think that either
of us would be here today
if it weren't for you.
So...
So get better.
And we'll be here
when you wake up.
Did you tell her I said hi?
I did.
All right, let's get out of here.
You okay?
I was just thinking
- about my friends.
Hmm.
They're all alone.
Right.
No one takes care of them anymore.
Can we visit them sometime?
Um...
You know what?
You never know what can happen.
Do you think if you drink
enough milk,
you just turn into a cow?
- No.
Would you start, like,
getting, like, spots on you
like a cow?
No.
- What would happen? Just...
♪ We're waiting every night ♪
♪ To finally roam and invite ♪
♪ Newcomers to play with us ♪
♪ For many years,
we've been all alone ♪
♪ We're forced
to be still and play ♪
♪ The same songs we've known
since that day ♪
♪ An impostor took
our life away ♪
♪ Now we're stuck here to decay ♪
♪ Please let us get in,
don't lock us away ♪
♪ We're not like
what you're thinking ♪
♪ We're poor little souls
who have lost all control ♪
♪ And we're forced here
to take that role ♪
♪ We've been all alone,
stuck in our little zone ♪
♪ Since 1987 ♪
♪ Join us, be our friend
or just be stuck and defend ♪
♪ After all, you only got
five nights at... ♪
Uh-uh. No, not today. Sorry.
I said, read the s...
♪ Five nights at Freddy's ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We're really quite surprised ♪
♪ We get to see you another night ♪
♪ You should have looked
for another job ♪
♪ You should have said
to this place goodbye ♪
♪ It's like there's so much more ♪
♪ Maybe you've been
in this place before ♪
♪ We remember a face like yours ♪
♪ You seem acquainted with those doors ♪
♪ Please let us get in,
don't lock us away ♪
♪ We're not like what you're thinking ♪
♪ We're poor little souls
who have lost all control ♪
♪ And we're forced here
to take that role ♪
♪ We've been all alone,
stuck in our little zone ♪
♪ Since 1987 ♪
♪ Join us, be our friend
or just be stuck and defend ♪
♪ After all, you only got
five nights at Freddy's ♪
♪ Is this
where you want to be? ♪
♪ I just don't get it ♪
♪ Why do you want to stay? ♪
♪ Five nights at Freddy's ♪
♪ Is this where you want to be? ♪
♪ I just don't get it ♪
♪ Why do you want to stay? ♪
♪ Five nights at Freddy's ♪
♪ Oh. ♪
M... E...
F... I...
N... D...
M... E.